http://www.spastaff.com/privacy

Love Spa Staff?
For easy access:
Click your browser's
menu:
Select "Add To Home Screen"!
Job seekers register now
> Already registered as a job seeker?
Employers register now
> Already registered as an employer?
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy
Spa Staff.com Limited is committed to protecting users' privacy. We will do our best to ensure that any information you give us remains private, other than for the purposes for which you have given it to us, as explained here and in our Terms of Use and Terms of Business.
We store and process information to improve our services
The data you give us is essential for us to provide you with the service of matching employment opportunities with CVs. Additionally, information gathered from users allows us to identify what works and what doesn't with our system, so that we can make it even more useful. Without disclosing personal details, we may share aggregated data with others, to enable us to design and implement improvements. Names and contact details will only be shared with your express permission. Candidates' identifying details, such as name and email address, will only be given to interested employers at the specific request of candidates. Only at your request will your email address be used to inform you of other services provided by Spa Staff.com, its affiliates or third party companies. Exceptionally, and only if required by law, your personal details and details of your usage of the site would be disclosed to the relevant authorities. By providing us with information you are consenting to our use of it as set out here. Any information you have provided to Spa Staff.com will be promptly removed if you ask us to do so in writing (or by email). Spa Staff.com Limited is not responsible for any inaccuracies in the information provided by you or anyone else.
Security of on-line payment transactions is not guaranteed
While personal and credit card details are handled by a secure server, we cannot guarantee the privacy of your personal and credit card details; nevertheless, the encryption used should be sufficient to prevent its interception in all but the most extreme cases. Contact us for more information on this if you wish. Spa Staff.com is not liable should there be a security breach, and/or any resulting misuse of your credit card details.
Cookies provide a richer online experience
A 'Cookie' is a piece of text data stored on your web browser, which can be used for a variety of purposes such as user name, passwords and preferences. You may set your browser to reject cookies, but the website's performance may be affected. Shared computer users should probably not choose to enable cookies. Data Protection Acts 1984 and 1998 apply; Spa Staff.com Limited is registered under these Acts, which are designed to ensure that personal data is held securely and processed fairly and lawfully.
Spa Staff.com welcomes your comments and suggestions
Your views are very important to us and are essential in helping us to improve our services to you. Any comments submitted become the property of Spa Staff.com Limited, and may be used for promotional or other purposes.
This Privacy Policy is subject to change
Any changes to privacy policy will be posted here, whether prompted by legislation or business needs. You should regularly check this page for such changes, as you will be deemed to have accepted them.
Terms of use and Terms of business also apply
This Privacy Policy, along with Spa Staff.com Limited's Terms of Use and Terms of Business, specify the basis on which the website should be used.
Company details
Spa Staff.com is the trading name of Spa Staff.com Limited, a company registered at Companies House for England and Wales number 7404037
Terms of Service
Terms of Business
Stay in touch
Twitter
Follow @SpaStaff on Twitter
Facebook
Like SpaStaff on Facebook
© SpaStaff.com 2020
Spastaff.com is a global online spa recruitment website for spa, salon and health club managers and their teams including massage therapists, beauty therapists, hair stylists, nail technicians and fitness professionals. We offer free adverts for beauty jobs, spa jobs, hair stylist jobs, nail technician jobs, fitness jobs and a free CV search facility of our extensive database of high quality spa job seekers - directly connecting the wellness industry and spa employers with spa job seekers both nationally and internationally.
Key Sections
About Us
Employers
Job Seekers
Current Jobs
Testimonials
FAQs
Blog
